{
    "id": "7f3626a64e6c4c759f243cdf2a902961",
    "title": "Modal Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………… you touch your toes without bending your knees?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Can",
                "May",
                "Shall"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5f7d74e24cbf4974bf480c96e223573d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… like to offer a piece of advice.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "could",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8cb66bcf07e248e09a186d21bc3fab36"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………….. you mind moving a bit?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Can",
                "Would",
                "May"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "296ac57b597c4c409cf3e0cbababc599"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. I leave now?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Can",
                "May",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1f8b86179fbd45b99e073f6b8ba35d4d"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………….. be sick your eyes are red and watery.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "can",
                "must"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "733eea91bbfb4aab95e83c0f527ffe22"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………….. not drink and drive.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "ought",
                "need"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a68c25ed46534328812a2d78a8ce4bc4"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… you like to have a glass of milk?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Can",
                "Would",
                "Should"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dec9ceab8829447da1e3622fcdc4e898"
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………….. have been in a lot of pain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "must",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bde2c8861ab5488fb6a34d2ac1ed1858"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………. build a rain water harvesting system.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "must",
                "ought to",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "ad88d02cc9254baf83b8571d8188e24d"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ...................... consume a lot of sugar, but now we have given up that habit.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "used",
                "used to",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cf2287510f38439ebc344e02c812dafd"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who ………………… it be?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "can",
                "may"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e891646ef6694c7fbec0b4945ce653d3"
        },
        {
            "question": "There ………………… be something wrong with him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "ought",
                "must"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c56aab4c8fc24dbca7d86666185c69bd"
        }
    ]
}